runkit.com 2017-10-07

# RunKit: Privacy Policy

Here's the `tl;dr`:

  * Documents created on runkit.com are **public**
  * We only ask you for the information we need.
  * We don't share your private information with advertisers.

Below is our privacy policy, adapted from [Automattic](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and available under a [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/) license, which means you're more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data, please [email us](mailto:support@runkit.com).

* * *

Stripe, Inc. ("RunKit") operates several websites including tonicdev.com and runkit.com. It is RunKit's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, RunKit collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. RunKit's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how RunKit's visitors use its website. From time to time, RunKit may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

RunKit also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users on runkit.com blogs. RunKit only discloses IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to RunKit's websites choose to interact with RunKit in ways that require RunKit to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that RunKit gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at runkit.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, RunKit collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with RunKit. RunKit does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Aggregated Statistics

RunKit may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, RunKit may monitor the most popular pages on runkit.com site. RunKit may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, RunKit does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

RunKit discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on RunKit's behalf or to provide services available at RunKit's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using RunKit's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. RunKit will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, RunKit discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when RunKit believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of RunKit, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an RunKit website and have supplied your email address, RunKit may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with RunKit and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. RunKit takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. RunKit uses cookies to help RunKit identify and track visitors, their usage of RunKit website, and their website access preferences. RunKit visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using RunKit's websites, with the drawback that certain features of RunKit's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If RunKit, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that RunKit goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of RunKit may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, RunKit may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in RunKit's sole discretion. RunKit encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
